May
Japanese Female Idols
Female Idols
Female idols
I want to be a woman who secretes something that stimulates me.
I simply can't come up with it.
There are things that can be created only because of us
We have been facing it with all our strength
For us
The new school leaders are my youth.
PHILOSOPHY IT
Haaaaah!
re
car
me
ch opposing
Thank you for watching.
You know you want it.
These glossy lips
Men of the mountains
make me breathe Breathtakingly sweet water
I know, you want it.
Nice to meet you, I'm Suzuka from New School Leaders.
I am Kaon of the new school leaders. Nice to meet you.
I am Rin of the New School Leaders.
I am Miki of the new school leaders. I am Miki of the New School Leaders.
I have always liked to do funny things, since I was a little girl.
I even aspired to be a comedian for a while.
But I was a bit twisted, you know, in the past.
I used to be naughty.
I was told I was cute, but I wasn't.
I was always told I was a tsundere.
I have a big bun here, here, and here.
I can't give up the three-tiered hairstyle.
I was cutting myself a lot earlier.
I've conditioned it and it's perfect now.
I have an older sister, and she has joined Kumi Koda's fan club.
She has seen Kumi Koda perform at big venues like Saitama Super Arena,
So I was rather influenced by her.
I was dancing like bling, bling, bling.
When I was in junior high school, I was practicing for an interview with the principal before the entrance exam,
I remember sitting like this and talking with the principal,
In high school, I had already decided on a career path for the Leaders, or rather, what I was going to do as a Leader,
I had decided in high school that I was going to be a leader, or rather, I was going to be a leader, so I was a little tsuntsun,
I was told that only a handful of people would be able to climb to such a high level.
So I remember thinking to myself, "I'm going to make the principal look back at me.
Next time preview
I like you, I like you, I like you, I like you, I like you, I like you, I like you, I like you.
You're a liar, and I really hate bastards like you.
I don't like, don't like, don't like, don't like, don't like, don't like
This is my bike.
Oh, man.
It's cool.
I printed it about three years ago with a friend.
How old were you?
I'm 21 now.
That's amazing!
This is Momoe Yamagishi's playlist
Momoe Yamagishi's Farewell Concert playlist.
And I recently started listening to
Jeff Backway
A friend of mine told me about him.
And when I was listening to it
It's so cool that it's already shaking my heart.
I only found out about it two days ago.
I didn't know there was such a legend.
I also heard Yoko Inoue's album "Ballerina".
She's playing Yoko Inoue's album Ballerina.
Momoe Yamagishi, who plays on Yoko Inoue's album Ballerina
I have a great admiration for the world of 80's songs
I've always had a great admiration for the world of 80's songs.
I somehow managed to find the depth of that era
and the depth of that era
and the strength of determination
I wonder how I can do something about it now.
Happiness in life comes in many forms.
I think that the four of us can make our dreams come true.
I don't know what it is, but it's like we're diving into infinite possibilities.
I don't know what it is, but we're just diving into the infinite possibilities.
And once we see that goal, well...
I think we should look for a different kind of happiness.